ISHA MHATRE



About Me

Hello, I'm Isha, an Information & Experience Designer, recently crafting GenAl led enterprise experiences at TCS. To me, UX design is about humanizing technology. I strive to create seamlessly intuitive experiences to make life simpler for everybody. I've always considered people to be at the heart of the design process and I believe that creative collaboration between design and technology is the magic that takes experiences from good to great! I've freshly graduated with B.Des in User Experience design and specialize in UX Research, UI Design and Design thinking. I think when we understand human-human interaction, only then can we design efficient human-technology interaction.

I love having conversations with different people; I think that helps me communicate with my team efficiently and bring a surge of energy to every project I work on!

Experience

TCS Research and Innovation
Jan 2023 - July 2023
Led a team of 6 in crafting GenAl
led enterprise experiences over a
duration of 6-months. My key

contributions include:
• Stakeholder interviews

- Fully-functioning Prototype
- UX research in GenAl led experiences

Madad.info

May 2022 - July 2022 Summer Internship Role: To design and develop scalable MVP, focusing on organizations in Maharashtra.

Education

2017-2019

Completed 12th from Dr. Kalmadi Shamarao Junior College, Pune in Science Stream and IT as optional with 70%

2019-2023

Bachelor of design in User Experience Design from MIT Institute of Design, Pune (7.9 CGPA)

Compentency

UX Research . Design Thinking . Wireframing . Rapid prototyping . Usability testing . Contextual Inquiry . Journey mapping . Information architecture . Problem solving . Interaction design. Competitive analysis

8484908158

ishasmhatre@gmail.com ishamhatre.github.io